https://toesocks.co.uk/privacy-and-cookie-policy/

We value your privacy This site uses cookies to provide you with the best experience. By clicking "I accept", you accept our use of cookies. There are various ways in which we will process your data, including personalised ads and content, which will be shared with some of our partners. Learn more. More Options Allow Cookies BackWe value your privacyOn this page you can set your preferences with regards to how we will process your data and share it with other organisations.REJECT ALL ACCEPT ALLGoogle AdwordsWe would like to share your onsite browsing and purchasing data with Google in order to show you targeted advertising via the Google platform. They will become the controller of your personal data, and you will need to contact them directly to exercise your data rights. A controller determines the purposes and means of processing personal data.View the Google Adwords privacy policy.SAVE & EXIT
Menu
ESSENTIAL
Silk Mid-Calf
Anklet
Mid-Calf
Knee-High
Over-Knee
Men Plain
ESSENTIAL
Unisize/Cotton/PlainUnisize (UK 4-11)
Anklet
Mid-Calf
Knee-High
Over-Knee
Unisize/Silk2 Sizes
Silk Foot-Cover
Silk Half
Silk Mid-Calf
Men/Cottton/Mid-CalfUnisize (UK M 7-13)
Men Plain
Men Business
View All Essential & Fashion FASHION
Unisize/Cotton/StripyUnisize (UK 4-11)
Stripy Anklet
Stripy Mid-Calf
Stripy Knee-High
Stripy Over-Knee
Unisize/Silk2 Sizes
Silk Foot-Cover
Silk Half
Silk Mid-Calf
Men/Cottton/Mid-CalfUnisize (UK 7-13)
Men Business
Men Argyle
Men Stripy
View All Fashion SPORTS
Trainer3 Sizes
Light Runner Trainer
Running Trainer
Micro-Fibre
View All Outdoor YOGA & PILATES
Half Toe / CottonUnisize (4-11 UK)
Anti-Slip Half Open-Toe
Foot Cover / CottonUnisize (4-11 UK)
Anti-slip Foot Cover OM
Ankle/Anklet/Cotton3 Sizes
Anti-Slip Trainer Serene
Anti-Slip Trainer
Anti-Slip Trainer Open-Toe
Anti-Slip Trainer Open-Toe&Heel
Mid-Calf/Cotton 3 Sizes
Anti-Slip Mid-Calf
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie NameCookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Performance Cookie:
These cookies are performance cookies. They help us to improve your experience on the site. For instance, we can provide better support with live chat which widget embedded on the site.
The only third-party application we use on our site is Zopim Live Chat. Please see below the steps to consent us to share cookies of this third-party application.
Zoopim Live chat:
ENABLE: To enable the live chat and use it so send any queries directly to us, please click enable cookies and chat as shown in image below. This will work as an opt-in consent to allow cookies to send any message to us.
If you change your mind, you can just click "Disable Chat" button and chat will be disabled, and cookie not will be used. In order to start chat, just click "Cancel" and live chat will start again after.
DISABLE: If you would like to disable the cookies, please follow the instructions below: (opt-out)
Click the "cookies" link on the bottom of the window.
Click to "Disable Chat" button to disable the chat and cookies will not be shared anymore. You can enable the cookie anytime you wish by going through step above called ENABLE.
Copyright © 2001 - present TOETOE, Ltd. All rights reserved.
